Hello,
Okutman: Merhaba,
and welcome to the course curriculum overview.
kurs mfredatna genel baka ho geldiniz.
In this video,
Bu videoda,
we're gonna be getting a brief overview
bu derste verilen tm
of all the content in this course.
ierie ksa bir bak as kazanyoruz.
Let's go ahead and get started.
Hadi balayalm ve balayalm.
First, this course starts off
Birincisi, bu ders,
with an introduction section
bu genel bak, Python 2'ye
including this overview,
kar Python 3 tartmas ve
a discussion of Python 2 versus Python 3,
bu dersi almanzdan elde ettiiniz faydalar en st dzeye
and a lecture on how best to approach this course
karmak iin bu kurala en iyi nasl
to maximise your benefits from taking this course.
yaklamanz gerektiine dair bir ders ieren bir giri blm ile balyor.
After that, we'll get started with the Python Setup section.
Bundan sonra, Python Kurulum blmn kullanmaya balayacaz.
We'll learn how to instal Python on your computer,
Python'u bilgisayarnza nasl kuracanz reneceiz, evre
we'll learn about environment selection,
seimi hakknda bilgi edineceiz, Jupyter
we'll learn about the Jupyter Notebooks system.
Notebooks sistemi hakknda bilgi edineceiz.
You'll get access to additional learning resources online,
evrimii olarak ek renme kaynaklarna erieceksiniz
and then we'll have a brief overview on Git and GitHub.
ve ardndan Git ve GitHub hakknda ksa bir gzden geireceiz.
Next, we start with the live code sections.
Sonra, canl kod blmleri ile balyoruz.
We'll learn about objects and data structure basics
Numaralar, dizeleri, listeleri, szlkleri, tuple'leri,
including numbers, strings, lists, dictionaries,
dosyalar, kmeleri ve Boolean'lar ieren
tuples, files, sets, and Booleans,
nesneler ve veri yaps
all in Python.
temelleri hakknda Python'da reneceiz.
After each of these individual lectures,
test etmek iin ksa snavlar var.
there's quizzes to test your understanding.
Bu bireysel konferanslarn her birinden sonra, anlaynz
And at the end of this section, there's an assessment test
Ve bu blmn sonunda, bu konularn her
so you can check your knowledge
biri hakkndaki bilginizi
on each of these topics.
kontrol edebilmeniz iin bir deerlendirme testi var.
Afterwards, we'll go to the section on Comparison Operators.
Daha sonra, Karlatrma Operatrleri blmne gidiyoruz.
We'll learn about both basic operators
operatrleri hakknda bilgi edineceiz,
and chained comparison operators,
bu blm de anlaynz test
with this section ending with a quiz
etmek iin bir testle bitiyor.
to also test your understanding.
Hem temel operatrler hem de zincirleme karlatrma
Then, we'll move onto Python statements
Ardndan if deyimleri, dngler, while
including if statements, for loops, while loops,
dngleri, aralk ilevi ve liste anlama dzenleri
the range function, and list comprehensions,
de dahil olmak zere Python ifadelerine
all in Python.
Python'da devam edeceiz.
With an assessment test at the end
Anlaynz test etmek
to test your understanding.
iin sonunda bir deerlendirme testi ile.
Next, we'll learn about methods and functions.
Sonra, yntemler ve ilevler hakknda bilgi edineceiz.
What they are, how to create them.
Ne olduklar, nasl oluturulaca.
We'll also learn about Lambda expressions,
Ayrca, Lambda ifadeleri, i ie
nested statements in Python,
gemi ifadeleri Python'da ve
and scope in Python.
kapsam Python hakknda da reneceiz.
We'll top it off with a homework assignment
Yntemler ve ilevler hakkndaki
to test your understanding about methods and functions.
anlaynz test etmek iin bir ev devi ile balayacaz.
Then, you'll have your first milestone project
Ardndan, Python ile bir oyun
where you will create a game with Python.
yaratabileceiniz ilk kilometre ta projenize sahip olacaksnz.
Then, we'll move on to objected oriented programming
Ardndan, objeler, snflar, yntemler, devralma
where we will learn about objects,
ve zel
classes, methods, inheritance, and special methods
yntemlerin Python'da renilecei nesnel
all in Python.
ynelimli programlamaya geeceiz.
Then you'll get a homework assignment
Ardndan anlaynz test
to test your understanding.
etmek iin bir ev devi alacaksnz.
After that,
Bundan sonra,
we'll learn about errors and exception handling in Python
hangi hatalarn, hangi istisnalarn olduunun ve nasl kullanlacann,
including what errors are,
kabul etmenin ve son
what exceptions are,
olarak hatalar ve
and how to use try, accept, and finally
istisnalar ilemez hale gelmesini ieren Python'daki
to handle errors and exceptions.
hatalar ve istisna ileme hakknda bilgi edineceiz.
Then, we'll top it off with a test
Ardndan, bilgilerinizi ve kursunuzdaki imdiye kadar
to test your knowledge and your understanding
yaptnz anlay test etmek
so far in the course.
iin bir testle balayacaz.
Then, you'll come up with your second milestone project
yaratacanz ikinci kilometre ta projenizi hazrlarsnz.
where you're going to create a more complex game
Ardndan, Python'da daha karmak
all in Python.
bir oyun
Afterwards we'll learn about Modules and Packages in Python.
Daha sonra Python'daki Modller ve Paketler hakknda bilgi edineceiz.
How to create them,
Onlar
how to instal them from the internet,
nasl oluturabilir, internetten
and we'll explore the Python Ecosystem in general.
kurabilirim ve genel olarak Python Ekosistemini kefedeceiz.
Then we'll move on to built-in functions in Python
her eyi ve hatta karmak saylar
such as map, reduce, filter, zip, enumerate,
nasl ele alacamz Python'daki yerleik ilevlere geireceiz.
all and any, and even how to deal with complex numbers.
Ardndan harita, azaltma, filtreleme, zip, numaralandrma, hepsi ve
At the end of this section,
Bu blmn
we'll have a final assessment test
sonunda, dahili ilevler hakkndaki anlaynz
where you can test your understanding
test edebileceiniz son
for built-in functions.
bir deerlendirme testi yapacaz.
Next, we'll learn about decorators in Python.
Sonra, Python'daki dekoratrleri reneceiz.
A three part series ending with a homework assignment.
Bir devle biten  blmden oluan bir seridir.
Afterwards, we'll learn about Python Generators,
ieren Python Jeneratrleri hakknda bilgi edineceiz.
including iteration versus generation discussions,
Ardndan, Python Jeneratrleri hakkndaki bilginizi
how to create generators, and a homework assignment
test etmek iin yinelemeyle nesil
again, to test your knowledge about Python Generators.
tartmalarn, jeneratrlerin nasl oluturulacan ve bir dev atamasn
After that, we'll put together everything you've learned
Bundan sonra, rendiklerinizi nihai
in a final capstone project.
bir kaptanlk projesinde bir araya getireceiz.
But that's not all.
Ancak hepsi bu kadar deil.
There's advanced bonus content,
ierii ve gelimi Python
including an entire section about Advanced Python Modules,
nesne ve veri yaplar var, bylece bilginizi seviyelendirebilirsiniz.
and advanced Python object and data structures,
Gelimi Python Modlleri hakknda
so you can level up your knowledge.
bir blm de dahil gelimi bonus
There's new content regularly added to this section
Dzinelerce dersle bu blme dzenli olarak
with dozens of lectures.
eklenen yeni ierikler var.
You'll also get access to community forums,
Ayrca topluluk forumlarna eriebilir
and dedicated help from me, your instructor.
ve benden, eitmeninizden zel bir yardm alabilirsiniz.
So, that's the entire course curriculum overview,
Yani, btn ders mfredatna genel bak, o
so let's go ahead and get started with the course.
yzden devam edin ve dersi almaya balayalm.
Thank you, and I'll see you at the next lecture.
Teekkrler, bir sonraki konumada grrz.